Friends with Brews. I have a sound clip that'll play later. Yeah, you used a sound clip
No, I have a sound clip that I'll play later that you sent me
You probably don't even remember sending it to me now
I probably don't ha but who are you for me to be sending you sound clips? It's in the show notes
My name is Scott for that matter. Who am I?
What the hell what is going on something is playing music in your house
[MUSIC PLAYING]
There's a lady downstairs playing with my Sonos,
and she probably just told it to play everywhere.
This was not planned.
Give me a second.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
That's hilarious.
Either that or--
It just stopped.
It's either that or the A word heard.
Alexa, what did you just hear?
Yeah, 'cause I stopped it.
I haven't heard anything in the last minute.
You can listen to all your requests
in the privacy section of the Alexa app.
I don't know if that's the kind of music
she'd be listening to or not.
Anyway, where were we?
I don't know.
I'm Scott, you're Peter.
We have brews.
What are you having for,
wait, what kind of brews are we talking about today, Scott?
I have already got mine in the show notes.
I have a coava San Marcos Honduras.
Honduras.
It's rich and chocolatey.
It has pear, brown sugar, and baker's chocolate.
Ooh.
Yeah, and it's pretty good.
It's not as amazing as that sounds,
but that could also be because I need to experiment
a little with the grind and maybe the brew on this.
Okay.
Not all coffees are the same,
but I tend to grind them the same and brew them the same.
Really? Not all coffees are the same.
I mean, there are a lot of people who-
Ooh, that's good though.
You probably don't realize that.
That's pretty good.
I think I would buy that again.
I'll have to experiment with the grind a little bit
and see if I can get it just a little smoother.
That's pretty good.
Well, I, sir, am drinking a counterculture slow motion.
And as the name may imply, it is decaf.
Peter isn't slow, oh.
Well, I am, because I'm drinking decaf.
This is actually my fourth cup of coffee for the day.
I had three cups this morning before like 9 a.m.
And then I didn't eat anything until after like one o'clock.
And that's when I finally had a lunch break.
Uh huh.
So, counterculture, slow motion.
Bladder doing.
Decaf.
Yeah, so counterculture, slow motion, decaf.
I like this.
I don't know, I've had one of their other coffees.
It's I think called 46.
I don't remember if we talked about that
on the show yet or not.
But I like it.
And this is good.
It's tasty.
It's just a tiny bit more acidic than I like,
'cause when I go to decaf,
I just go usually with the Wegmans store brand,
decaf espresso roast.
Anyway, I like counterculture.
Like I said, slightly more acidic than I like, but good.
This is definitely a drinkable coffee.
I probably will buy it again eventually,
but I am trying to vary and branch out a little bit
and try new coffees.
So every time I go to the store,
I buy a different cup of something or a different bag of something.
Yeah, I'm definitely trying to do that too.
But my problem is it also affects my wife because coffee bags are
expensive. We both drink coffee.
And it's pretty rare that I can justify buying a stash for myself.
And I actually, I can be price sensitive with things.
Yeah.
And I, as you've heard me say many times on this show,
I, you know, my default coffee is just the Wegmans store
brand espresso roast.
I really like it.
I don't buy it just cause it's like one of the cheapest
thing, I think the Dunkin Donuts stuff might be cheaper.
It's really my favorite coffee that I can get at the store.
So I go to something like this, which costs maybe twice
as much as theirs and I'm like, okay, it was fun to try.
I'm going back to the old reliable.
Yeah, and that's fair.
Like coffee is one of those things where I don't know why but the way I brew it maybe
is more sensitive to it but it's easy to get a bitter cup of coffee if you're not careful
and a lot of coffees that people like aren't that smooth and yeah we are also people that
tend to fall back on a couple really beloved favorites.
I do say beloved.
By the way, I also have the very flat and very rectangular chocolate chip cookie that
my wife made.
This is homemade.
Anyway, it's good with coffee.
I imagine it would be.
Before we go on, a question.
Your favorite recording software for the Mac, you're using Audio Hijack Pro?
Is that correct?
Audio Hijack.
And Audio Hijack.
It's just called Audio Hijack now.
Oh, it's not.
Okay.
So if I was to buy it, it's okay because I'm not a pro when it comes to this.
You will be if you buy it.
And that's Rogue Amoeba software, correct?
Yeah, yeah.
Wait, wait, wait.
Are they just Rogue Amoeba?
Yeah.
Rogue Amoeba.
Okay.
So I use Piezo because it's charmingly simple.
Right.
Charmingly simple.
It's a little too simple.
It's a little too charming.
Well, I'm starting to get to that point.
There are things when I would like to be able to do with, for example, does audio hijack
support the mute function?
you mute while you're on a recording? I'm gonna go with no because you're thinking
about this way too much. I think the answer is no because I think I say I'm
not a hundred percent sure. I'm trying to remember if you mute it if it will also
pause that recording. What you want it to do is keep rolling and fill the track
with silence no matter what's going on. I think the answer is no. I think the answer is no.
Okay okay no that's that's fine I was just curious about that. That is a
feature that I'm kind of missing so I was just wondering if that was gonna be
filled by that gap. The Snowball is USB right? It is USB old which means I have
it running through an adapter to get onto my Mac MacBook now. What is Fission?
Rogue Amoeba Fission. Fission is just a very simple audio editor I actually use
it for what do I use it for I use it for making clips like a lot of the sound
clips that I have in my my soundboard okay they go through fission so I can
normalize them and clip off parts that I don't want or join sections together and chop out
stuff in the middle stuff like that.
So it's not something you would use to edit a podcast but it's certainly something you
can use to clean up audio files for general purpose use.
Okay.
I don't do much of that and the audio hijack folks, they're pretty contained to audio stuff,
right?
They don't do like screen captures and stuff?
Correct, that's right.
Screen flow or whatever.
Okay, I'm just curious.
Just curious.
Okay, okay, all right. I think that's all the questions I have right now.
The piece of software of theirs that I use in order for you to hear the soundboard,
for me to be able to play the soundboard and you to hear it, that's Loopback.
And basically what I can do in Loopback is create a microphone,
a virtual microphone, that's really my mic plus Forago, which is the soundboard app.
Forago?
Yeah, and so that means that it all comes through the microphone setting in FaceTime,
so you can hear it too.
Okay, okay, cool.
Alright, I feel like I've gotten a little bit of education.
I was trying to see if there was a USB version of what I'm using for my mic, because it's
got a capacitive touch.
See, I just muted it.
All I have to do is touch the top of the box and it goes mute.
It's called a Wave XLR.
It allows me to set things like clipping protection.
I listen to my headphones through it.
My mic goes into it.
My mic's an XLR though.
And then volume, gain, all that kind of stuff in addition to the mute.
And the nice thing about the mute is I can set whatever colors I want when it's recording,
when it's taking input, and whatever colors I want when it's muted.
So I know when this thing is muted.
All I have to do is look at it and look at the LEDs and I know that I'm on mute or not.
It's really nice.
But the fact that they call it Wave XLR makes me think there must be a USB version, but
right now I'm failing to find one on their website.
Something like Wave USB?
Wave DX?
I don't know.
All right.
Well, anyway.
Anyway, whatever.
Who cares?
Exactly.
Obviously we do, but that's not why we're here today.
What are we here to talk about and record about and things?
Mission, quest, thing.
I... you gotta look at the website for Hollywood Theater.
There is this theater in Portland.
Portlandia?
Called Hollywood Theater.
It's in the Hollywood district of Portland.
Yeah.
And it's a theater that's been around for a long, long, long time.
It's historic, but it's basically kept going by donors and members.
So basically people will buy memberships and make donations and that's what allows them to keep going.
They've got 70mm projectors which are really hard to find now.
And so they're always on the lookout for trying to find backup equipment and find replacement equipment and stuff like that.
But anyway, the version of 2001 that we watched on Saturday, they had made specially for them.
Because when they first opened Hollywood Theatre a long time ago, or reopened, I can't remember,
They had a copy of 2001 and it wasn't that great.
So they actually got themselves working with the movie company
and some 70mm film producers, of which there's only one company that deals in anymore.
They actually got themselves a custom reel, or however many reels.
They got a custom copy of 2001 in 70mm and it's really nice.
It looked really good.
It was a lot of fun.
This place is crazy.
They've got a pipe organ and it's a real pipe organ.
All the pipes are behind the screen.
They weren't doing anything with it when we were there, but they can.
You would love this place.
I wish we would have gone to this place when you were here.
Sounds kind of cool.
And you can sit in there and eat slices of pizza and drink beer
while you watch the movies.
I mean, that sounds even better.
Yeah.
All right.
So what else are we talking about?
I don't know.
What do you got?
So I have been, as you know, I have been using Edge, uh, Microsoft
Edge, the chromium based version.
I know.
Um, pretty much since it came out and overall I liked it and I liked the
synchronization across platforms. I liked not having another Google thing as my primary
everything. I understand that. And it just plain does not work with some websites. So here's the thing
I know that a lot of people hate Firefox, but
Firefox actually is not a pig anymore. It's actually a better performer now than Chrome
They go through phases though, don't you think? I mean, you know, they go through cycles. So does Google. Google is a resource hub.
Oh, absolutely. This is why I wanted to stop using Chrome for the longest time and I did.
But is Microsoft Edge that much better? It's based on Chromium.
It's based on Chromium, yes, but there's a lot of stuff that both Google and Chromium are, I mean,
Microsoft are adding after the fact that really significantly changes the browser.
Right, but my impression was the engine itself is pretty garbagey.
I don't know about that. I mean, we've got, wait, how many different versions are there now? There's WebKit and there's Chromium?
No, WebKit's not Chromium.
Right, but that's two. Those are two engines. Are there any others? Or is everything WebKit and Chromium these days?
I don't know what Firefox is using, to be honest. Firefox is using their own, aren't they?
I don't even remember. I feel like I should know this and I feel stupid for asking.
Ahh... buh buh buh buh buh buh... it uses the Gecko rendering engine.
Latest version of Firefox uses gecko Safari and Chrome use WebKit. There we go. So it's Safari that's using WebKit
I don't believe that Chrome uses WebKit anymore. Chrome used to use WebKit and then they forked it off into chromium
It's not the same as WebKit anymore
Okay, so seven years ago. Yes seven years ago. They did use WebKit then they forked so developer
"mozilla.org has document that says 'applications based on WebKit or Blink, such as Safari and
Chrome blah blah blah." Now that document was updated in September, but that doesn't
mean it's current.
I don't think Chrome uses WebKit.
Why don't we ask? Let's go and say, "Is Chromium based on WebKit?" Is Chromium based on Firefox?
WebKit and During Engine share between Safari and Chromium. So says chromium.org.
But here back in... it does, but I remember back in fact here's a link right here on 2013 saying
it was built on WebKit and then they forked it and in Wikipedia under WebKit it says WebKit
is used as the rendering engine in Safari and was formerly used by Google Chrome.
Chrome used only WebCore and included its own JavaScript engine. I know Chrome has its own
own JavaScript engine because that v8 JavaScript engine is what what node uses
that's definitely different than WebKit okay all right so the iOS version of
Firefox uses WebKit because I don't think well they have no choice right
yeah Apple doesn't let anybody they have no choice exactly exactly but yes it
uses gecko it does use gecko but does Chrome okay is still use WebKit sure
That's the question I was just answering.
And then the answer was what?
Chromium.org.
We do not actually use the layer Apple calls WebKit.
See?
Got it.
Okay, so what's it called?
It's a rendering engine?
Chromium.
Okay, so it's just its own thing.
Yeah.
Got it.
Okay, got it.
WebKit, no.
Chromium, yes.
Okay, so we have three major things out there.
the webkit chromium and gecko and I would wager that any other weird
browsers probably use chromium to opera I don't know I haven't looked at brave
is opera even still a thing brave is just Firefox no is it isn't yeah no
brave is no it's based on chromium it says right here okay sorry
Tor is just Firefox. Tor is Firefox just reskinned. Brave. Can I say this out loud?
Brave is like the browser that people who are paranoid but not real tech savvy go to. That's my impression.
Yes, Opera is chromium based and Vivaldi is just Opera, right? I don't pay attention.
I don't I don't I don't see the point. I don't understand it. Yes. Okay, so it's also chromium based. So yeah.
Yeah, I have not been paying a lot of attention to these alternate browsers. Yeah
Yeah, I have an idea.
I am starting to use Safari a little more
just because there are some things that it does better
like integrating with hide my mail and SMS.
When I get prompted for two-factor codes in a form fill,
I can do that.
So that's kind of cool.
And it does integrate across all my Apple devices.
Yes.
It doesn't integrate across my Apple and Windows devices.
And that's where Edge had the upper hand.
But I'm actually now going through a phase
where I'm segmenting off my browsing.
And I'm actually using Chrome again for one reason,
because I just found out about Chrome profiles,
or just rediscovered them.
I hadn't been using them for a while.
So you can have a-when you sign into the browser,
you can sign into your Chrome browser with a Google account.
And I have a number of different Google accounts.
So it's nice, because one of them is strictly for a client,
one of them is for Paradigm, and one is for my personal stuff.
So to have three different browsers, three different sets of extensions, three different
sets of bookmarks, kind of cool.
And it really, it's nice because I just fire up this browser.
I become Peter at Paradigm and boom, I see all my Paradigm tools.
I come over to this client account.
I have all those tools.
I come to personal and I don't have any of those tools, but I've got my own fast mail
and other stuff that I want to see.
So it's, it's kind of neat.
That is really neat.
Uh, Safari doesn't have anything like that.
What it does have is it has tab groups.
And I've been using tab groups.
Like I've got a programming tab group, I've got a web development tab group, I've got
actually different programming tab groups because I've got one for like Python right
now that's stuffed with all the Python stuff that I'm learning.
I've got one for SwiftUI.
But my main complaint about the way they do their tab groups is anytime you click a link
in any other app, it jumps back to the default group and opens it in that. And I hate that.
I hate that behavior. And not only that, if I have a window with like 20 tabs, a lot of
times a link will just open in its own window. I don't want two windows. I want one window
with a billion tabs.
I was getting really confused because I had Safari as my default browser and somehow I
I was clicking links in Gmail and in Chrome and it was spawning Safari.
Right.
And I was like, wait, where did that just go?
Where, where did my email go?
I'm so lost.
So that was kind of funny.
But I'm curious to hear a little bit about Python.
Talk to me about Python.
Cause I did use Python like it was 2003 when I dove into Python.
That was back in the Python two days, right?
Oh yeah.
Oh, absolutely.
Now there's a segmentation.
You have to choose. Are you going to use Python 2 or are you going to use Python 3?
And I'm using Python 3.
If you're starting with new, you want 3 because 2 is like, it's going away rapidly.
Yeah. But the reason I started using it was I was playing with...
I thought I would just write a quick script that gets a list of the people that follow me on Mastodon and keeps track of them.
So over time, I'll be able to look at the changes in my followers.
And the first library that I came across that looked like it would help me integrate with
the Mastodon API was one called Mastodon.py.
So I thought, "Okay, I'll do this in Python."
I've always wanted to actually program a utility or do something in Python anyway.
We use it all the time at work, and I've looked at Python scripts and edited them, but I've
just never actually sat down and wrote anything with it.
So I started using it, and I'm really surprised at how full-featured Python 3 is.
And the first thing I noticed was the logging, because in JavaScript with Node scripts, I
a third-party utility called Winston. And it's got super good logging. Well, Python
has pretty much the same level of logging built right in now. So it's clear that they
focused on certain specific things, and I really kind of like it. And as I go through,
I'm finding that a lot of this stuff, I don't know if it's just because this is my nth language,
or if it's just because Python makes discovering some of the concepts easier, but figuring
it how to do something that I would do in a node script or some other language in Python
has been really easy for me.
Okay. I remember when I started with Python and I mean I have to I've seen some Python
3 which it doesn't look materially it's the same like you know it's an evolution language
right right not apparently like what Perl 6 apparently I haven't even like followed
like was did Perl 6 even become a thing and apparently they named it Raku and changed
it so it's so different, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah.
Didn't it become object-oriented at some point?
Was that before the
Wall?
I met Larry Wall in 2005, and he was presenting at a conference.
And he had the slide, if it was 2005, let's say it was 2005, and he had a slide and the
projected release date for like real Pearl 6 was 2004, a year prior.
And I raised he had any questions.
I said, yes, are you still on time on target with that release date?
And he looks at it, he turns around and says, yes.
It became clearer over time, like it was never happening.
And I was back, I was in the like the Pearl, like Pearl was like a thing for me.
I had all the books and I was everything I could program.
I was programming in Perl.
It was great.
It's a lot of fun.
Is your name John Siracusa?
No.
Oh.
And then I did start playing around with Python and I did really like it.
And I thought the learning curve for Python was trivial easy to get started.
Trivially easy.
Perl is a particularly obtuse language.
Not if you're already familiar with Bash and C.
I was familiar with C before I started with Perl and Perl still looked like some a$$---e
designed it just to piss people off.
It can be, but I used Perl as a better C than C. So that's why a lot of my Perl code looks
like it looks shockingly like C code.
In fact, some of it could probably even compile, but that was for me, it was just like, oh,
it's like C only I don't need to declare my own string type and stuff like that.
It was really cool.
But Perl gets real hard real quick when you want to do really fancy things.
Python I found the same way.
It's like, you know, Python was like, "Wow, this is so easy.
This is so easy.
Wait, how the hell am I supposed to...
I don't get it."
It was like everything was going fine and I got up to like 65 miles an hour and then
I hit this brick wall with advanced data structures and things.
I don't even remember exactly what it was that I couldn't wrap my head around.
But for basic scripts and stuff, I liked it.
I think the fact that I just went through a longer learning curve with Node and a lot
of that ecosystem and learning about some of the things that are typical with it really
helped me come up to speed really fast on Python, like package management, how to install
packages locally so that you can develop them while you use them, et cetera.
All that kind of stuff, I had to learn that the first time when I did it with JavaScript.
And though it's different with Python, a lot of these languages do a lot of the same kinds
of things now, as you would expect.
Right.
So, question on that.
Did you consider Golang or Rust when you decided to learn this new program language?
Rust looks interesting.
Golang?
I hate Go.
I really do.
And I know a lot of people like it.
Part of the problem I hate Go, though, isn't really Go's fault.
Part of the problem I hate Go is Go templating languages' fault.
And when we were messing around using Hugo for the web, that's go templating language.
And it made me want to kill someone and I still want to kill those people.
And but more appropriately, we use Python all the time at work.
It's used for tons of different scripts that we have that it makes way more sense for me
to, to dig into Python than it does for me to learn go or rust because nobody in my job
is going to be using those.
Yeah.
Isn't rust a compiled language?
The rust and go are, they're both.
So the reason, the things I'm using Python for are like server scripts and utility things.
Things that will run on a server, they don't need to be super performant, but yeah.
Yep.
And for those, I generally, if it's on Linux, I generally still drop into Perl.
Yeah.
And if it's really, really small, I'll do bash, but otherwise it's Perl.
And if it's Windows, I try to do it in PowerShell.
And again, for simple stuff, like it's easy.
And then I can do some stuff with PowerShell syntax just wraps my brain.
It is weird.
I don't get it. It's it's like wow in Perl I would just do this but in PowerShell
I need to do this to this to this to this, but that's actually an interesting project
I should I should throw those over at ChatGPT like how would I express this Perl code in PowerShell and see what it says?
I'll bet you it can translate
PowerShell is weird because one of the guys I work with is really pretty good at PowerShell
And I look at some of his stuff, and I'm going oh, that's great
And then I get to something and I'm like how would you have ever known that like?
Yeah, exactly. How am I supposed to know that? I don't know.
I don't know.
Oh boy. So yes, I'm having fun with ChatGPT though. It's interesting, asking the things that I can throw in AI.
I guess... It's not that I don't think it's fun. I know I've been cranky about it.
What makes me cranky is the people who seem to take it super seriously, like it really is doing amazing things. It's regurgitating huge data sets.
Sure, but it's always people that are making you cranky. That's what they do people make us cranky. Well, it's not my fault that people are
But no, but a lot of people like I think some people are overestimating what it's actually doing. Yeah
For example when it comes to writing samples, it's a cliche machine like it just scours a lot of bad literature
Clearly nobody bought a bunch of expensive really good books for it to read
Programming-wise, both Stack Overflow and GitHub claim that the problem with it is it creates reasonable-looking code that's wrong.
Right. I mean wrong. Right. And if you ask it logic questions,
it also comes up with the incorrect an-like, it's not good at logic puzzles. So what you're saying is, before I
turn any
junior developers or analysts onto this
thing they really should know what they're doing first because otherwise it's just gonna be like just mashing fingers on a
old-school calculator and
Just trusting any number that you get back from it if you actually want to use this code
You will have to have somebody that does know what they're doing review every bit of it, right?
Otherwise you're just gonna copy. Well, this is what it told me is fine, right? Yeah. Yeah. Yeah, that's that's problem
That's a problem, but it's interesting. I just think that
I'm a little worried about people's over-reliance on things they don't understand.
[Laughter]
I think we're seeing the evidence that the people who are religious about their tech and think they're changing the world aren't necessarily to be trusted.
And the people that don't understand the tech aren't to be trusted either because they'll believe in stuff that clearly is voodoo.
Huh? What do you mean? Don't trust my code.
Speaking of not trusting things, let's talk about Twitter real quick, because I've got about 10 minutes where I have to leave the house.
There's something to not be trusted. Yeah.
So we haven't talked about Twitter in so long.
I know. But you sent me the sound clip a long time ago, and I meant to play it last time and I didn't. But you can talk about this a little bit. What is Smashing Security?
Smashing Security is a podcast hosted by Graham Cluelly and Carol Terrio. They're both ex-Sofos employees.
Oh, it's funny. It's I'd say maybe it's my third or fourth favorite security podcast at these days
at this time. But yeah, it's pretty funny. And they generally have a good sense of humor,
a lot of injected into their shows. A lot of it's, you know, somewhat British humor because Graham
is British. But I also really like a lot of their co-hosts. And that was where I found out about
the cyber wire because Dave Bittner is an occasional co-host he's the host of the cyber
wire but they also have others who are just you know like interesting co-hosts so I use them to
find more sources of of information but anyway yes I sent you a clip from the Smashing Security
podcast but I don't remember which one it was here it goes I thought he was spending 44 billion
dollars on buying Twitter. Turns out that's not the case. Is it not? No. What's he buying?
What he's actually done is he's spent 44 billion dollars promoting another service,
which many people won't have heard of before, called Mastodon. Yes. Twitter, yes, exactly.
You know who Joshua Topolski is, right? Josh Topolski, whatever he calls himself?
He's the guy that started The Verge way back in the day.
Oh, okay, sure.
He's not the guy that runs it now, but he started it, and he said, he claims,
and he has screenshot evidence of his claim, that links to Mastodon are getting flagged as
sensitive material on Twitter now. I'm talking about general links to Mastodon,
not links to specific sensitive content on Mastodon.
Oh, I believe that. I believe that.
Yeah, but-
They're just not even trying to pretend not to abuse their position anymore.
I mean, the Twitter files thing should have told everybody.
They basically just handed over all private internal communication to a couple journalists.
Which seems insane to me, but whatever.
So I don't use Twitter anymore.
I don't have Twitter on any of my devices.
I don't go there anymore.
I've made my Twitter accounts private.
And if you try to tweet it, friends with brews on Twitter, I won't reply.
Cause I won't be looking.
So use the link for the friends with brews account on Mastodon and go there and I will respond.
Interesting.
Okay.
I just can't stomach it anymore because it really has gotten worse.
And I really feel like it's just becoming a raging far right love fest with Elon Musk.
and every time he says something incredibly stupid, all his fanboys pile on.
And anybody who says anything halfway reasonable just gets dog piled.
You see, this is something, this is a little bit of a mystery for me because I assumed
that a number of his fanboys, I mean, if they're fanboys first, then okay, I get it.
I assumed that a bunch of his fanboys were eco-friendly, eco-warrior, tree-huggers, left-leaning
liberals.
You would think so.
But you know what's funny is I don't think Elon Musk ever really was.
I don't think that's why he got into the electric car business because right now Twitter is
pushing a lot of anti-climate change conspiracy theories.
This is depressing.
It is.
It's worse.
So a friend, a good friend, my running buddy a couple of weeks ago sent me a picture of
himself on his commute into the office.
He works down at MIT.
He sends a picture of himself.
He's wearing a beanie and it says SpaceX.
Oh no.
And he says, "This used to be my favorite hat. Now I'm not so sure."
And I sent him a picture of my Tesla and I said, "This used to be my favorite car.
And now I'm not so sure."
Yeah, his beanie's a little more easily replaced than your car.
I bought him a replacement beanie for Christmas. So yes, I already replaced his beanie for him.
He has not yet reciprocated by giving me a, you know, like a Kia EV6 or anything.
But I'm hopeful. I'm still hopeful.
I mean, red isn't my favorite color in the world, but there's no way I would ever wear any kind of red hat now.
At all. Ever.
I do have a red sweatshirt, an upgrade sweatshirt that I bought a few years ago, and I still wear it, but...
Red doesn't do good things to me anymore.
It's similar to that. It'd be like if I had a red beaniea red cap, a red baseball cap of some kind.
Like, if I was a Cardinals fan or something, or, you know, whatever, Phillies or something.
And then I'd be like, "I don't care. I know that it's got a different logo on it, but I don't care.
I can't wear this stupid red hat anymore."
That's... it's really sad. But understandable.
Not really, because it's one ofit's not the greatest color.
That's what's funny, is like, it just goes back to Trump's inherent bad taste.
[inhales]
[exhales]
That's what he picked. That's what he picked to be associated with. But whatever.
I like it. I like it.
Anyway.
Oh, man.
So I heard you talking with Adam today, not talking today, but I heard it today because it
came out today on blurring the lines and you were saying that so far your nose situation is going
well. Yes, yes it is. You can blow your nose now? I can blow my nose with wild abandon and so far
no repercussions. Good. So yes, yes I'm very happy. I felt for a little bit, it was about
two days ago I blew my nose a little bit and I had a little bit I smell I thought
for sure I smelled blood oh no and I thought that I had reinjured you know
reopened the wound and didn't happen I was hallucinating I was just being
paranoid so that was kind of cool well if you're gonna hallucinate I can think
of we should come up with a list of other things because there's better
things than blood bloody noses to hallucinate about gross gross oh brother anyway what else
we got that's pretty much it for me all right no that's good because we're getting close to time
you've got but you've got something else to do i did yeah i do i did give you guys some feedback
though on your uh podcast because adam was talking about making bread and you suggested beer bread
I did. And I have to say that not only does beer bread help with the dough rising process,
it's just really freaking good. Yeah. Makes me wonder, I have this like 14% alcohol, chocolate,
raspberry beer, and I can't drink it. Okay, the point isn't for the bread to make you drunk,
Peter. Well, the thing is, I can't, well, all the alcohol would bake out, but I can't drink it,
though because it's a it's a pint and I try drinking one of these like almost a year ago
when I got it and I was like I could only get a third of the way through I'm like I
literally cannot finish this it's too sweet it's too strong it's too syrupy but I'm wondering
if I was to put that into a loaf of pumpernickel raspberry chocolate pumpernickel bread just
let that I'm just gonna leave that's on that note I'm just gonna leave it right on that
Just see what happens. You're gonna push the big red beer bread? Big red beer button. Yeah, big red beer button.